# Sean M. Kennedy

# Chicago, IL | 312.320.7318 | sean47900@gmail.com | LinkedIn | GitHub

# **SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS**

Highly motivated team player, whose previous work experience has sharpened multitasking and interpersonal skills. Creative, resourceful, and flexible in navigating unfamiliar situations or tasks. Effective working independently or in a group setting to accomplish goals.

### **Skills**

HTML | CSS | JavaScript | Python | React | Node.js

### **PROJECTS**

# PropertEAZY (<a href="https://properteazy.netlify.com/">https://properteazy.netlify.com/</a>)

A property management application that aims to streamline communication between owner and tenant.

React | Node.js | SQLite | PostgreSQL | Material UI | Express | Helmet | Morgan | Cors | Knex

- Payments made easy with Stripe Connect for rent payments
- File uploading so that contracts and photos of maintenance needs can be sent between tenant and owner
- Design is responsive to mobile, tablet, and desktop views

#### **EDUCATION**

## Ball State University, Muncie, IN

2013 - 2017

Bachelor of arts Degree in "Telecommunications and Emerging Media"

### Lambda School, Remote

2018 - 2019

Full stack web development and computer science.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Markey's Rental and Staging, Merrillville, IN

2017 - Present

- Organizing and tearing down audio, video, and stage equipment
- Constructing stages for presentations
- Running camera and recording speakers of presentations

# Northern Trust Bank, Chicago, IL

• Facilitating video and audio conferences with partners of the bank all over the world

2017 - 2018

- Answering hotline calls and troubleshooting problems with partners
- Schedule and plan meetings with partners to ensure effective communication

## On Campus Internship

# **ESPN 3 Ball State Video Boards, Muncie IN**

2016 - 2017

- Facilitated both handheld and stationary cameras for televised sporting events on Ball State campus
- Organized production of setting up and tearing down all audio and visual equipment